iofferphoto.com 2011-12-16

# iOffer: A Place to Buy, Sell & Trade

At iOffer, we take your privacy very seriously. Please read this privacy policy (the "Policy") to see how iOffer handles your personal information that you give to us when you register with our website (the "Site"). This Policy is an agreement between iOffer and you, as the user of iOffer’s website. This agreement tells you when the policy is effective, what information we collect from you, how we might use it, how you can review or change the personal information provided to us, how we may change this policy, and the steps we take to ensure that your personal information is protected. 

All activities you engage in on the Site are voluntary, and you are not required to provide any personal information to us unless you choose to access features on the Site that require the information. If you do not agree to the terms of this policy or the Site's other terms of use, then you should immediately exit and discontinue using the Site. iOffer's terms of use are expressly incorporated herein by reference and made a part of this policy. By using the Site, you signify that you agree to the terms of this privacy policy as well as to our terms of use.

Our main purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with an enjoyable, customized, and efficient experience on our Site. It is our policy to never willfully disclose any personal information about our Members to the general public without their consent. iOffer collects information from you when you register and conduct certain activities on the Site. We collect your full name, valid telephone number, contact/billing information, email address, and physical address. Also, each Member must create a unique user id and password. We also collect financial data (such as your credit card or debit card number). If you communicate with us by e-mail, post messages to any of our chat groups, bulletin boards or forums, or otherwise complete online forms, any information provided in such communication may also be collected. Any additional information collected will be used in accordance with our privacy policy. 

We also collect some information from your browser. This includes your IP address which enables us to identify your computer or device on a Transmission Control Protocol/Internet Protocol (TCP/IP) network, which includes the World Wide Web. This general information (including click stream data and cookies) may be collected from you whenever you access the site whether or not you provide us with any personal information. This information helps us to diagnose problems with our servers and administer the Site, and helps us in identifying you and your specific needs.

We may use click stream data (i.e., server address, domain name) to analyze and better customize your visits. Such uses may include traffic analysis or ecommerce analysis of our website to determine which features are most or least effective or useful to you.

We may also use cookies to gather information about your visits to the iOffer Site and enhance your user experience. Cookies are software tags that are stored by your browser onto your hard drive for identification purposes. These bits of information are general in nature and they allow us to customize our Site to fit your specific needs and preferences. Cookies also allow you to log onto or navigate through specific sections of our Site without having to re-enter certain information. You can turn off all cookies, in case you prefer not to receive them. You can also have your computer warn you whenever cookies are being used. For both options you must adjust your browser settings (such as Mozilla, Firefox or Internet Explorer). There are also software products that can manager cookies for you. Please be aware, however, that when you choose to reject cookies, this choice may limit the functionality of the iOffer website and you may lose access to some of its features. 

We will not sell or rent your personal information to anyone

  * We will not give personally identifiable information to advertisers;
  * We utilize safe, secure technology to protect your personally identifiable information;
  * We do not tolerate spam.

The financial data collected from iOffer is to bill you for iOffer’s services. Other information collected from iOffer Members is used to improve product offerings, customize our Site's content and layout, and for marketing and statistical efforts. Occasionally, we will send you emails about new services or promotions. You can always opt-out of receiving any information from us, but please understand that such a request will likely limit your ability to take advantage of all of the features and services available on iOffer. 

Our number one priority is to keep your personal information private and confidential. Except as set forth herein we will not willfully disclose your personal information to third parties. And we will not rent or sell your personal information to anyone. However, certain personal information will be made available to others in the process of using our Site. This information includes:

  * Other visitors to our Site may view your user ID, rating, city, and other items you have for sale;
  * In order to complete the transaction, the buyer and seller are provided with each others email and postal address;
  * When making an offer, the seller can view your user ID, rating and your city. 

Of course once you provide personal information to a buyer or seller on our Site, iOffer has no control over how that information is used by that individual. You should discuss any privacy concerns you may have with any individual you meet through our Site, as the only protection you will have is whatever terms you agree to directly with this individual.

In addition, we provide some of our services through contractual arrangements with affiliates, services providers, partners and other third parties (collectively "service partners"). Our service partners may use your personal information to operate our sites and to deliver their services. For example, your data may be transferred to website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in designing and operating the website, executing services or helping us analyze collected data. These parties will only use your data for the purpose of carrying out the work as agreed with us and will be required to keep the information confidential. We will encourage our service partners to adopt and post privacy policies. However, the use of your personal information by our service partners is governed by the privacy policies of those service partners and is not subject to our control.

iOffer will disclose your personally identifiable information to others under the following circumstances:

  * You consent to share the information;
  * In response to subpoenas, court orders or legal process, including from jurisdictions outside the United States;
  * Your actions on our Site are, or appear to be, in violation of the Terms of Service and disclosure of this information will assist in efforts to enforce the Terms of Service;
  * You post a listing which iOffer believes in its sole discretion may create liability for iOffer and disclosure of this personal information may minimize or eliminate its liability.
  * For security purposes or to prevent imminent harm to any person or entity
  * To cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal purposes.

We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful, as determined in our sole discretion. Release of your personal data for security purposes, as described in this agreement to any person or entity under any circumstances shall be based on a determination made solely by us, exercising our sole discretion, permission for which is expressly granted by you to us in accordance with this policy.

Nothing in this Policy shall limit, prohibit, or otherwise deny the ability of iOffer to (1) transfer, assign, or sell its assets, including, without limitation, the assets of our Site, to a third party or (2) dispose of its assets in any manner through bankruptcy or similar proceeding. iOffer also makes no representations regarding, and disclaims all liability arising out of or related to, the accuracy or completeness of the information it collects and discloses through our Site.

In an effort to keep your information confidential, iOffer provides its Members with the highest industry standards for secure servers - Secure Socket Layers (SSL) and firewalls. We provide you with the capability to transmit your personal information via secured and encrypted channels if you use a similarly equipped web browser. Unfortunately, perfect security does not always exist on the Internet (or in the real world). Despite this, we will do our best to continue to ensure the security of your private information.

You may cancel your registration at any time. You may modify your personal information by logging in to our website and visiting your registration page at www.ioffer.com/user/edit and following the instructions provided. We encourage you to promptly update your personal information when it changes. 

Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information online there is a risk that third parties may intercept and use that information. While iOffer strives to protect your personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online. By using this Site, you expressly acknowledge and agree that we do not guarantee the security of any data provided to or received by us through this Site and that any personal information, general information or other data or information received from you through the Site is provided to us at your own risk, which you expressly assume.

Only those who are 18 years or older may use iOffer. Personal registration information submitted by a person under the age of 18 will not be accepted. Any general information provided by a person under the age of 18 and gathered (for instance, through the use of cookies) during his or her visit may be used as indicated in this policy. iOffer is committed to protecting the privacy of children and has no intention of collecting personal data from children under the age of 18. We encourage parents and guardians of children under 18 to regularly check and monitor their children’s use of email and other activities online. If we learn or have reason to suspect that a user of iOffer is under age 18, we will promptly delete any personal information in that user’s account.

We go to great lengths to protect all of your information on our Site. To help us maintain the security of your personal information, we ask that you do not share your password with anybody. Sharing this information could put you and your rating as a buyer/seller at risk. If you lose control of your password or you think that somebody has obtained unauthorized access to your account, immediately change your password. Please contact us if you have any questions.

You must promptly notify us if your credit cared, user name or password is lost, stolen or used without permission. In such an event, we will remove that credit card number, user name, or password from your account and update our records accordingly.

iOffer sometimes contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We sometimes also make chat rooms, forums, message boards and news groups available to you. Please understand that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. We have no control over its use and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

This Policy, as modified, is effective as of July 15, 2009, and will remain in effect except with respect to any provisions that are changed in the future, in which case the changes will become effective on the date they are posted on the Site or we otherwise notify you of the changes. We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update, or modify this Policy, simply by posting such change, update or modification on iOffer and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update or modification will be effective immediately upon posting to this Site. You should check this policy periodically as its terms may change from time to time. Your continued use of the Site after we post such modifications will constitute your acknowledgement of the modified policy and your agreement to abide and be bound by the modified policy. We will also revise the "last updated" date found at the beginning of this privacy policy when we post changes to it. 

Your opinion truly counts. Our Site was designed to serve the needs of our Members. Please contact us with any questions or comments. You may do this by sending an email to the iOffer Customer Service Requests Page.
